// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
      question: "What of the following is the default value of an instance variable?",
    answer: "Depends upon the type of variable",
    options: [
      "null",
      "0",
      "Depends upon the type of variable",
      "Not assigned"
	      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the size of double variable?",
    answer: "64 Bit",
    options: [
      "8 Bit",
      "16 Bit",
      "32 Bit",
      "64 Bit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the default value of char variable?",
    answer: "/u0000",
    options: [
      "/u0000",
      "0",
      "Null",
      "Not Defined"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the default value of Boolean variable?",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      "Null",
      "Not Defined"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is instance variable?",
    answer: "Instance variables are variables within a class but outside any method.",
    options: [
      "Instance variables are static variables within a class but outside any method.",
      "Instance variables are variables defined inside methods, constructors or blocks.",
      "Instance variables are variables within a class but outside any method.",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is static block?",
    answer: "It is used to initialize the static data member., It is excuted before main method at the time of class loading.",
    options: [
      "It is used to create syncronized code.",
      "There is no such block.",
      "It is used to initialize the static data member., It is excuted before main method at the time of class loading.",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Static binding uses which information for binding?",
    answer: "type.",
    options: [
      "type.",
      "object.",
      "Both of the above.",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is synchronization?",
    answer: "Synchronization is the capability to control the access of multiple threads to shared resources.",
    options: [
      "Synchronization is the capability to control the access of multiple threads to shared resources.",
      "Synchronization is the process of writing the state of an object to another object.",
      "Synchronization is the process of writing the state of an object to byte stream.",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What will happen if static modifier is removed from the signature of the main method?",
    	answer: "RunTime Error: NoSuchMethodError.",
    options: [
      "Compilation Error.",
      "RunTime Error: NoSuchMethodError.",
      "Program will compile and run without any output.",
      "Program will compile and run to show the required output."
    ]
  },   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "which operator is considered to be with highest precedence?",
    answer: "i() , []",
    options: [
      "() , []",
      "=",
      "?:",
      "%"
    ]
  },

];